So I have made The Root 100. I want to shout out The Root for recognizing me as one of the
top 100 Black people that have influence and be doing shit. I'm going to fight y'all for
choosing this picture. I am going to fight y'all for choosing this picture. Yep. I'm going to fight
y'all for choosing that picture. Y'all, this is a picture of me at the US Open after hours of
like watching tennis. All these pictures that you could Google that I spent so much money to take.
And this is not about Even The Root, but this is as a request. Y'all stop billing me as an actress
first. Please, please stop billing me as an actress first. I'm out here. I'm a comedian.
I'm a social justice advocate. I know I was on a show, Insecure, but acting is like the least
important thing I do. That said, I do appreciate the acknowledgement and, you know, being out here
as a truth translator is no easy feat. That's why you see me glistening so much right there
because I'm sweating. Thank you, Root.